<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Super Productivity</string>
  <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">Super Prod</string>
  <string name="webview_block_message">Please update Android System WebView to version %1$d or newer.</string>
  <string name="webview_init_failure_message">Super Productivity could not start Android System WebView.</string>
  <string name="webview_init_failure_details_with_provider">This is not an outdated WebView version. Android reports WebView provider details, but the provider fails during startup. Try updating Android System WebView or switching away from a beta provider in Android WebView settings. Avoid removing WebView updates unless you have exported or backed up your Super Productivity data; sync may not include local unsynced changes.</string>
  <string name="webview_init_failure_details_without_provider">This is not an outdated WebView version warning. Android could not start WebView before provider details were available. Try updating Android System WebView or switching away from a beta provider in Android WebView settings. Avoid removing WebView updates unless you have exported or backed up your Super Productivity data; sync may not include local unsynced changes.</string>
  <string name="webview_block_detected_major">Detected Chromium major version: %1$d</string>
  <string name="webview_block_detected_full">Detected WebView version: %1$s</string>
  <string name="webview_block_provider">Provider package: %1$s</string>
  <string name="webview_block_source">Detection source: %1$s</string>
  <string name="webview_block_update">Update WebView</string>
  <string name="webview_block_open_settings">Open WebView settings</string>
  <string name="webview_block_close">Close app</string>
  <string name="webview_block_try_anyway">Try anyway (not recommended)</string>
  <string name="webview_manage_warning_title">Manage Android WebView?</string>
  <string name="webview_manage_warning_message">Android may show options such as removing WebView updates. Removing updates can clear WebView storage on some devices. Continue only if you have exported or backed up your Super Productivity data; synced data may still require reconnecting accounts and local unsynced changes may be lost.</string>
  <string name="webview_manage_warning_continue">Continue</string>
  <string name="webview_override_warning_title">Continue at your own risk</string>
  <string name="webview_override_warning_message">Your Android System WebView appears to be older than version %1$d.\n\nIf the version reported above is correct, continuing may cause:\n• The app to crash or fail to load\n• Data to render incorrectly or not at all\n• Sync errors and possible data loss\n\nVersion detection is occasionally wrong on certain devices. If you are sure your WebView is up to date, you can continue — but please update Android System WebView from the Play Store first whenever possible.</string>
  <string name="webview_override_warning_continue">I understand the risk, continue</string>
  <string name="webview_override_warning_cancel">Cancel</string>

  <!-- Share intent -->
  <string name="share_received">Content received, creating task\u2026</string>

  <!-- Startup overlay -->
  <string name="startup_overlay_add_task">Add task</string>
  <string name="startup_overlay_hint">Add a task while loading\u2026</string>
  <plurals name="startup_tasks_queued">
    <item quantity="one">%d task queued</item>
    <item quantity="other">%d tasks queued</item>
  </plurals>
</resources>
